you're all watching here's the first
Fallen just short might have fallen Jess
short would have been a dramatic start
to the Innings ball swung late
yes I think the ball dipped into him and
that's the reason we had to check his
shot at the last moment
swinging Yorker
didn't quite get it
and you might think right left-handed
have done well against India this
pressure on the bat
there's pressure on the bowler too it
was 160 is the kind of score where you
need to get off to a really good start
even for the bowling side
it's a very competitive total it's a
very very competitive total eight runs
Anova is the asking rate for India
now this was a
Shaheen Shah fredi
against India in that the 20 World Cup
last year just watch the lengths he's
giving the ball time to swing
Bennett swings back is when the danger
was where was that day and could be
today
it's live in place too
[Applause]
side edge
not base that it's always the moving
ball that troubles you always does
not the pace so much
because the batsmen are so used to going
and playing through the line and when
that late movement happens like this one
then you get an Inside Edge you can see
that uh Rahul is looking to push at the
ball now that is sometimes can be a
little bit of a dangerous thing
because what you want to do
is to ensure that there's not much of a
gap between Batman particularly because
he's swinging the ball in
Mario Rasmus has gone running all the
way there
oh there's something something on that
side screen that's shining that's
reflecting the lights
just the placards that have fallen on
the screen
right how are we going to get these out
[Music]
now I think Rohit Sharma said Let It Be
doesn't bother me Let It Be
so I think play will start
that's interesting one one opening
Batson was getting distracted the other
said doesn't matter to me
so whatever it was that was distracting
kale Raul is still there but he's at the
non-strikers in
now what
[Applause]
I don't think batsman like this
as he opened the stands just a little
bit that's the interesting thing Rohit
Sharma he does open his stance against
the left hand over the wicked baller
and he's off the mark too just erring a
little on the fuller side so far Shaheen
Afridi yes I think what we saw when he
played that warm-up game the other day
we were looking to get that in swinging
Yorker where he hit the Afghanistan
opener
by nastily on the tall he's looking to
get that going
but both times it has been no full
tosses
drop back
now trying to angle the ball from a
little further outside off
then they're too far outside off
you look at the history of
competition the history of contest
between these two skewed very heavily
India's way
look at the last three games Pakistan
2-1
you can see Rohit sharma's backlift is
very very minimal
very very minimal he's aware of the fact
that Shaheen shafridi can get the ball
to nip back in
you can see that it's not as high as
normally is that's a smart thing to do
have a look at that back here very
minimal hardly goes above the shoulder
hardly goes about the shoulder
he started off about 132 that last ball
was 140.
three of the over so far
put it in the Gap it's just a little
push
should be good enough for two
but he was in control first over gone
fight for no loss with a proper 45
degrees but on the on side is backwards
Square about 10 or 15 meters inside with
45 inside the circle on the onside
[Applause]
he's playing a little bit across the
line Rahul
what Nasim is trying to do is get the
Fuller length going
because the ball of Fuller length you'll
get the ball to move just that little
bit and he's got the extra face as well
so this is a smart bowling
all he wants to do is make sure he
doesn't go too full this is the length
this is the length that you want to bowl
this length very well in the initial
overs for India
just wonder whether he wants to get that
ball to swing off middle stump he's got
extra support at midwicket now
[Applause]
if it's a big day
they saw what their new ball goal is did
it's a wonderful recovery from Pakistan
to come so far
maybe the dusting it's okay we'll
counter the swing there's runs to be had
afterwards
see the white ball doesn't move too much
after say about four or five hours
well what is field 360 telling us with
Nasim bowling to Raul
see the spaces
on the boundary
back for two
and that's the thing about these big
boundaries
you can get two runs comfortably if the
ball is about five or ten meters to
either side of the Fielder
comfortably go for two that's exactly
what the Indians have done
right where are the spaces those are the
two men on the boundary
anything in front of the Wicket if you
can beat the court in this point
discover this mid off that's where the
runs are
well
docking 143 142 already
I said this is just the first over
wanted to get a little more confidence
when he knows his run-up is right he's
not going to overstep then you can
really let it drip
it's virtually a full house at the MCG
then if you if you're coming in here a
little early you could see the
enthusiasm around they've come from a
long distances to come and watch this
game
oh it's been on he's played on Gail roll
once again
and he threw his head back in
disappointment as that happened nothing
in charge produced the Breakthrough
that's the extra Pace it's the extra
base that has got the ball to go on to
the stumps he played with a soft bottom
hand and with that soft bottom and that
would have gone back just a little bit
have a look at that yes and that is what
happened it would have hit his back leg
and then gone on to the stumps
that is the Breakthrough that Pakistan
were looking for
Gail Rahul
is gone
before India lost their first week at
First Seven
[Applause]
Virat Kohli in at number three
first ball Naseem Shah to Virat Kohli
squared up a little bit this is a good
opening burst from the young man
seven for one
[Music]
it should be a good contest Sharma
[Applause]
hi the travel just inside though
wide marker
clever clever bowling he was getting the
ball to nip back in in the previous over
this time he angled the ball across to
the right-hander but this is the Wicket
this is the wicked of kale Brown look at
that
playing onto a stumps he's been balled
three times against the pakistanis
how can he get it this long back
and take the single
and you're not going to get too many
boundary balls so you've got to be alert
to the single with our colleague at the
non-strike as in this always always
looking for that single
we're not going his record against
pakistanis is very very good
in recent times is the incoming ball
that's troubled him a little bit more
but there's one player who's probably
the opposition is most apprehensive
offensive Virat Kohli additional man in
the covers
and again
he's just inducing the angle
is he setting up Virat Kohli
getting the ball to go straight with the
angle that's what he's done
look at his t20i career look at
opposition against Pakistan 406 Runs at
67.7 the striker drops a little bit
against Pakistan but he puts runs on the
board that is what India hoping today
this is a little drizzle around
finds the gap on the offside
it's a long boundary can they come back
for three twos on twos what they're
happy with
very good shot the kind of shot that
gives the batsman a lot of confidence
might not have been a boundary but look
at that footwork very positive leaning
into the drive as well and then finding
the Gap he wasn't looking to hit the
ball too hard because it's still new
it'll move a little bit so that's very
good bad thing by Virat Kohli now Afridi
goes round the wicket
[Applause]
McCauley has had a few problems against
the incoming delivery
Ball moving in
particularly in the white ball game look
15 times he's got out to The One moving
in
just one of the fact that he's gone
round the wicked try and angle the ball
in
is it not swinging enough
oh it's a good ball he's doing too much
I think
is doing too much they're all very
excited Mario erasma says no
stand for one
they were very excited
but you can see that wall has hit him
high up on the thigh
so they'll be very happy with the dot
ball didn't want to refer it to the TV
Empire
Pakistan past Bowlers can get yes Irish
rauth
[Applause]
shine shaft really he went round the
Wicket to Virat Kohli and there it is
that ball has come back in it would have
gone over the top of the stumps that's
why they were excited but they knew that
with the height that giant shaft really
has with the bounce that he can generate
there was no point wasting on a review
yes appeal by all means appeal but don't
go for a review
I wonder how Pakistan are going to play
this India had 16 overs I've seen
Pakistan f-12
[Applause]
Edge The Edge as it carried I think it
they think it has Android Sharma is
moving away
Irish Rove has produced yet another big
breakthrough the slip was there for it
and India have been robbed at Denver two
tentative poke
you can see it's a very tentative book
Ballers bounce a little bit so
absolutely catch this is a terrific cat
it's a low catch these are not easy to
take because against the fast bowler you
expect the ball to come around Johnny
I think for fair catch soft signal is
out no yes
[Applause]
already in but they want to take a look
at the catch again I think you'll find
it's clean It's a Wonderful catch by if
the card
to go with his batting but the umpires
just want to be clear and the soft
signal is out
deeper do you have me Deepak for the
best angle for the catch please
interesting position bending but the
batsman's left
new batsman's taking guard
deep back do you have Richard here thank
you keep that rolling through please
keep it rolling through please keep it
rolling through please fingers clearly
underneath the ball I'm ready with my
decision for the big screen
[Applause]
it's better to be safe than sorry
I think by now Roy charma Degen spats
and pipe that off too
yes you would have seen it he saw it and
that's why he was shrugging his
shoulders when the Empire asked him to
wait he knew that the catch had been
taken clean he was close to the action
as well
and what Pakistan have done what Babar
Azam has done he's added another slip
he's looking for wickets to push India
back
straight down the ground by men who can
do no wrong in the form he's in
straight back where the bowler came from
for four
it was a wonderful shot this is a
terrific shot
get some swing
over pitching Harris you got a wicket of
the previous delivery getting the ball
to move move having fished it up but
this one maybe just a little too full
allowing to play this gorgeous straight
drive
counter punch
bomb he's in he's not going to hold back
that is the Wicket they want dare I say
even if gold is at the other end
shot in this land again finds a gap on
the offside
they run well they should look for three
here
and that's the kind of running that you
need because you're not going to get
boundaries easily while the ball is hard
new and the ball of the bowling so well
with two balls and he's got seven runs
the kind of form that he's in this is
the wicked
yeah look at that just attentive
pork at the ball outside the Austin fine
low catch diving to his right by with
the car you've got a very good half
century and now he's got rid of the
Indian captain
[Applause]
he likes to get off The Mark with those
dabs down to Third Man
good to see Charlotte comes and has a
laugh with him
Barber will do that too enormous amount
of respect in this Pakistan side for
Virat Kohli
Kohli
he's got a big job on his hands here
this is field 360 looking at it from
Virat kohli's eyes so what he's seeing
[Applause]
17 for two actions in world cricket
here Rahul and Rohit Sharma and Mohammad
rizwan and Babar Azam Pakistan 15 for
two India 17 for two there's Nasim
[Applause]
like a fast leg break wasn't it
and at that piss it's not easy to play
seem upright then after pitching it just
moves like a fast leg break
a little bit
[Applause]
a Leading Edge every ball is an event
here at the MCG today
and every ball was an event when ashdeep
Singh took the new ball early on
straight away babarasam with his first
ball
the shortfall to uh Mohammed rizwan
that was his third Asif Ali
very interesting to see how babarasam
rotates his fast bowlers
it's in the air but it doesn't matter
it's a long long boundary there can they
run three more
you'll hardly see threes when you see
T20 cricket played on the subcontinent
we've already had two so far in the
ceilings
a bit up in the air he likes to push the
ball away if it's around his hips
I feel it was
at the midwicket more towards midwicket
not towards the squalic Empire otherwise
it could have been a catch
but that is what India needed to just
break free after the first two dot balls
the pressure easing just that little bit
when you have three runs
here's something interesting now for uh
Virat Kohli the left cover open
brought an additional man into shot mid
wicket
[Applause]
beard
won't get the second that he wants
there's only one
again see that the ball is moving around
a little bit
because shakoli played
making the adjustment at the very last
moment to the movement to the ball
look at the way he strike trade against
bases 157 again spin 145.
06 than anybody else in 2022 that's a
shot that's fraught with Danger on these
colossal boundaries the MCG
[Applause]
thought during that little collapse in
Pakistan's middle order when Heather Ali
and if the car and
Shada all tried to play big shots and
got caught
these are Big boundaries
he's also the
actor
that's when I could take that into
account
when you go down you realize that there
is a stiff breeze blowing
[Applause]
not a battle with that for Pakistan
fight from it it's 22 for two
still there's Pace in this pitch
yeah and you just want to be back off
the land almost the Test match length
here because
the board is going off the straight
there's a bit of sea movement bit of
extra bounce
wouldn't really want to piss the ball up
just
stand it up back of a limb
immature really good shot it was just a
fraction short
very very quick eye
yeah just short of a land just too short
this time just marginally
[Applause]
Surya Karma yadavis
so quick at picking up the length
and then being able to execute it's off
the front foot
is just about the time that he's picked
up land and thought I'll pull this
lots of spaces go in the air
there's plenty of gaps there's still in
the power play
[Applause]
it's a club that's Pace it's bounce it's
everything for Pakistan an adventure man
is on his way back and not loving it
also done it again short of the lens
even more Biz this time around
been hit to the left side for a boundary
but he keeps pounding in
the sword is clamping up a room it's
just got big on him good catch from
rizwan in Pakistan
they are in this big time now huge
wicket
[Applause]
in India now 26 for three
[Music]
oh
except Patel is the new player for it
India elevated in the order left-hander
two slips
Patel is facing the music now from how
to roll
and he gets away and he should get two
how does Ralph is actually of all the
players out there got the most
experience of playing here at the MCG
and maybe he
had the assistance of that knowledge
with this delivery
kite in too tight to play a flat bat
shot
Saras Ralph played Seven matches for the
Melbourne stars in the BBL picking up 11
wickets in the process
none more valuable than that one though
let's look how far back the keeper and
the slipper
we see that please mate helped just how
far they're keeping the slipper back
yeah it's just about beef
he's running hard over 90 miles per hour
92 that last delivery
what is the pace and bounce and maybe
slow one but right now is just hitting
the Wicket but I I go back to just how
far the keeper and the slipper back
it's just staggering they're almost on
the circle now they're the belts the
bounce and the carry
just look how far that
is a long way back
[Applause]
now they might look for three here it's
quite nicely timed
although good Pace across the Outfield
brilliant brilliant over 31 for three
shut up comes into the attack from The
Shane warning
pretty good end to bring a spinner in
front
Pace would go out of the game somewhat
now
but we shall just see how Barbara's arm
continues to exert pressure on India
they can't let them collect freely
yeah
normally the go-to bowler for Pakistan
in t20is and
this situation India will probably be
thinking spin on time to attack
[Applause]
Runner should be fumble stuck still here
what a Miss what a complete and utter
Miss and it may well be the skipper
they've got it wrong
copy
umpire review for run out at the
Striker's end
TV Empire to director we have an Umpire
review for run out of the Striker's end
you'll see your best side on angle
please
I'm gonna need to see a view from front
on here please to see if the actually
the ball or the stumps break the wicket
keep that rolling through please
yeah keep that rolling through please
I'm gonna need to go back to your best
side on angle please I just want to make
sure that the ball breaks the stumps
before the wicked keep his gloves
yeah I'm gonna have to just see a split
screen on this please
keep it rolling through please keep it
rolling through please keep it rolling
through please
freeze it there please
yeah freeze it there please I'm ready
with my decision for the big screen
[Applause]
the biggest sigh of relief there because
his fumble and look at the celebrations
his Bumble nearly cost the opportunity
and there was another fumble but through
it all Pakistan get it right
[Music]
[Applause]
didn't work out for two is 31 for four
[Music]
[Applause]
nier is the new player for India Byron
Amis now and Pakistan they got a life
there because I firmly believe they
thought they'd got it wrong they went
back to their positions as if they
weren't going to get a chance
and they got rid of Exile Patel which
means hadapania comes out
but it was the case of fumbles
wasn't pure but it was effective
[Applause]
all a bit frantic
yes no send back Barbara misses it four
throw rizwan well he thought
that he lost it he didn't get it in his
gloves
his reaction was that
we've messed this up
because it's not in his gloves you are
absolutely right
both thought they'd got it wrong they
both thought they got it wrong the body
language was so obvious
and yet somehow they got it right
staggering fumble here
fumble there look at the reaction this
one's they
they cannot believe their luck
[Applause]
that is Mission has just informed us
should Isaacs and India have never won
when they've been 32 for four
[Applause]
so that will be a first
you can see Pakistan switched on
that new ball burst
now with their best bowler operating
pretty comfortable 33 for four India
[Music]
six for four then for their tie in
Durban they had the tie and Dave and we
had the bowl out remember that
now getting all of this from the
sideline
Square onto the Wicket
and Isha I've got to say from up here
there's some crazy stuff going on what
about down there
but it's all been happening I have to
say that I tell you what though the
Indian fans a little bit subdued at the
moment at the halfway stage they might
have felt they were in the game
especially with the batting lineup that
they had but Pakistan have been
outstanding they've believed in the
power play they've removed some key key
men and they're all up and about in the
stands currently but don't write India
off because varic Coley is still there
hard at Paddy we know what he can do
especially when he gets going but I
think that last Wicket was a crucial one
he's got to find an ally though who are
these allies
well it's got to be hard at pandya but
the reason I say that last week it was a
crucial one is because it means that
Mohammed Nawaz can come into his work
with that left hand are gone there's not
too many left-handers in this Indian
side so he has the chance to operate
against the right-handers I thought it
might have been a bit of a dilemma
for barbarism as to when to bowl him
as the fifth bowler but he's been able
to come straight into his work against
two right-handers
yeah excellent point excellent point the
good captaincy tell you to realize that
that window of opportunity the other
thing that happened to uh is well know
uh the right required run rate just
going up to 10. psychologically 10 and
over all of a sudden in difficult
conditions it seems
difficult conditions but when you've got
hard at pandia there you know you can
score at 12s 13s 14s and over so for
these two it's about rebuilding it's
about taking it deep like Ms dhoni used
to do we're at curly out in the middle
Virat can run quickly between the wiki
it still just wants to be listening to
work the ball and run those twos hard
and let's not forget Dinesh Karthik one
of the best finishes going around at the
moment
[Music]
[Applause]
yeah look for India now to win this this
next
12.1 always have to go completely their
way you don't have any sort of leeway
Pakistan at the moment passing the game
yes but
they themselves were 44 for two so
there's not much in it at this stage
[Applause]
right now won't hurt Pakistan but build
India in a ways 38 for four
the man at Center Stage here for that
Coley one thinks
nicely bald
I kept a single
and as you say
I will not mind singles Pakistan
big shots that are going to hurt them
they're going to get into your back in
yeah just in this sort of stairs that
middle over stage it's sort of mellowed
down
both sides happy to just sit back
Pakistan morsel
India have been forced to sit back
[Applause]
well we talk about uh who has to do it
well he's done it before
78 not out 57 55 not out
can he do it for a fourth time
[Applause]
the other great thing about having the
World Cup in Australia is that it evens
it up padding first batting second is
there's no Discerning factor of actually
uh added advantage of chasing
the continent you always want to be
chasing much easier back in second
Australia not as simple
well you did the pitch Report with
Michael Clarke and Michael Clarke said
get him on the board get them on the
board probably thought more than uh 160
but get him on the board indeed now
runs always crucial to have on the board
as we see in uh tournament play India
about themselves chasing but they've
lost some crucial wickets here
and with that bomb rate being driven up
you just think that
India will have to take a risk or two
against these Spinners he can't just let
them operate as they are at the moment
41 for four
promise you
should defeat nice piece of adjustment
too from Nawaz
a talked about the matchups the left arm
spin do the right-handed
I don't think they care about the
matchup Decay about the party here
Lakeside Pakistan Lego 99 of their final
10.
now India requires 118 so they'll have
to go some
and it was that little break in play all
that that Prince break that really
kicked Pakistan on after that
maybe India is trying to follow suit
look at rizwan that's beautifully placed
rizwan the keeper is sprinted 40 yards
instead three players have and that is
placement for Perfection absolute
perfection
just back pocket and came back for two
it's been waited beautifully
all that it didn't go anywhere near
those deep feelers and it was in the gap
foreign
[Music]
need a shot of authority in the end
as you say they might wait now they'll
reassess
and two balls time but they need a one
or two shots of authority just
psychologically to put Pakistan
slightly more on the back foot
the ones are fine they'll live with the
ones Pakistan
or two big blows if not now straight
after drinks
yeah I need you to throw some punches
right now everything in Pakistan's favor
one thing that India have come back with
almost halfway through the Innings and
just fours 4.47
[Music]
it ferociously had by haddock paneer he
did well
that was to Parry that away
it is uh 45 for four after 10 overs time
for a drink and time for both sides to
take stock here in Melbourne
the balance now the hard thing when do I
take a risk and how big a risk do I take
I feel like both Hardy can Veer out
there played so much T20 cricket two
class players so India probably couldn't
ask for two better players at the crease
but
it's going to work out what risk will
they take even they look to go hard
along the ground rather than try and hit
that ball over long off for long on just
to try and pick up a couple of
boundaries get some momentum good point
because they bought these borders the
Spinners they don't give too much air
especially shut up it's very difficult
to get under him and hit him for six
so that boundary option becomes
important where you've got to play the
field
so with Pakistan they took that chance
they broke away in two hours of spin
with five sixes and that got some
momentum
when you look at that Innings last 10
over is 99.
that's a fine shot hit hard into the
ground and down the ground for four
the way that I think that's class I
think it's smart fatty it's shortest
shortest boundaries straight look to hit
it hard along the ground you still get
that four I know it's sort of Maximum
but just a couple of those to build some
momentum then you might get a bad ball
you can take a a short for a pull shot
for six or a full toss for six I just
need some momentum
does pack a punch Our Big Pun dip
[Applause]
age of difference here is just the
wickets in hand it's when does India
press you know completely go if they're
two down they'd probably go now 10 overs
nine half overs to go but being four
down they might just have to these two
just go steady for might be two more
overs
that's the thing right yeah you
mentioned till when is it till the 12th
over 13th over
but after that both these players will
have to look for the boundary every hour
at least
but they don't want this uh required
rate to climb with the fastballers
coming back into the attack
all right
in the field cover comes to point as
well open up that offside
[Applause]
bowling
man on the boundary just another single
for India
and they'll be quite happy
52 for 45 becomes the first Indian who
is for over a thousand runs and take 50
wickets
T20 cricket V8 overall football
will get two
it's a good over from India's point of
view
nine off it 54 for four
here's mama dabaz
that's a good hit
first six of the innings
it's a great shot from Hardy pandya
stepped away made the following follow
him gave himself a little bit of room
here in Australia with that consistent
bounce he just swings through the line
he realizes he's a very good reader of
the game he captains aside in franchise
fricket
India need a move on here
they need to
get some momentum and put the pressure
back on the opposition
let them know that you're still coming
it's a good start to be over
for a small six
and smart buddy looking to go straight
got their field set up for hardik pundy
out a lot of Defenders a lot of fielders
defending that straight area they've got
instead of a deep point he's more of a
straight cover long off long on really
straight for Hardy pundia they want him
to go across the line
captaincy from Pakistan
yes it's the shorter boundary and that's
what he'll Target either along the
ground
or over the baller's head if he gets the
opportunity
[Applause]
he doesn't need the boundaries Hardy
could find those but if he can look to
get that ball in the gap
just not thinking about reviewing or
preferring this
a man from backward Point kept running
they have gone up
I think Inside Edge
copyright player review for court
original decision is not out TV Empire
director we have a player review for
court original decision is not out front
foot checked it's a fair delivery move
on to front on spin Vision please
[Music]
get that rolling through please
[Applause]
okay Paul is close to the bat we go to
ultra Edge when available please
Ultra Edge when ready please
still waiting for Ultra Edge
Ultra Edge coming up now keep it rolling
through please Flat Line there keep it
rolling through right through please I'm
trying to make sure it doesn't hit the
glove on the way out keep it rolling
through please keep it going right
through
right food
thank you I'm going to go back to rod on
field Rod you can stay with your
original decision of not out you're on
screen now signal really missing the
battle review gone
[Applause]
that's a good hit heal the police of the
feet second six of the over the first
football league
's confidence the world are good this is
a beautiful shot doesn't look there
doesn't look over hit it down the Wicket
good use of defeat
again shortest boundary the times is
beautifully head nice and still good
balance
just checks out beautifully
test the kind of all that India need
what two sixes they've got 13 off the
over that's some momentum going there
with still two balls left
smart bearing
[Music]
all peace players they've got the skill
they've got the experience they've got
the temperament for the big occasion
to get things moving very good balance
and he played it
hardik he knows
grabbing momentum
run rate coming down
getting a bit more control back India
[Applause]
that's six more
Stand and Deliver
three sixes in the oval
it's 20 off hits 74 for four
here's a pretty back in the attack
a big over Rafi big over from India
hardik started at first fully over
that's right out of the middle then this
the experience in class if you're at
Coley and hardik finishes it with
another one 20 off the over game on here
this is exactly how Pakistan Broke Free
with three sixes in an oval
but a good cricket from India targeting
the right areas
media change up pace being brought back
he'll want to here
and get it easily
and see the crowd warming up now we
realize this could be a real good
contest that's smart batting the MCG
plenty of those get the ball in the Gap
such a big ground particularly square of
the wicked
pick up lots of twos
[Applause]
oh good feeling
and keep the batsman down to one
[Applause]
so let's now go to a Magic Moment a year
ago tomorrow
[Applause]
this could be the moment this is the
moment
ultimate celebrate as with these two
young men out there
[Applause]
so here's a free thing
and beautifully flicked away
and find the boundary is using the pace
of the bowler and the angle
and the 50 partnership comes up
as it will here opens up this Lakeside
finally up inside the circle again angle
in uses the pace
on 40K he's off the bat even quicker
chipped in the air he'd get only a
single
nine of the over so far so India getting
those overs they want
see with this field as well at the
moment three out on the leg side India
anything to the leg side unless they get
at that League glance I think they're
going to look for two bunted towards
that midwicket mid-on Circle and push
for two their boundaries gonna be
through the offside I think Hardy's
going to look again either
I was gonna say I have a mid off but
Barbara's making a change now mid-off
goes back to Long off
third man comes inside the circle so any
width outside off you might see hardik
pundy trying to freeze hands
that's what he might not want to allow
him to do
pull into the stuns that's a beauty to
end the over 83 for four
but India will Target him in the silver
last over a spin we saw 20 taken
that's a good shot it's in the Gap and
it's traveling
and it beats the field
it's the boundary of the first ball
very powerfully struck
it's not the worst ball because the
captain's got the field set for him to
ball that leg he's got three men on the
cut shot
hurray call again timing the placement
he's got to get it in front of that man
and he does the man out on the
boundaries a lot straighter
very good batting good placement
foreign
[Applause]
I think he wants a maximum
so do they haven't they absolutely got
back into the game after that big over a
20.
[Applause]
this one there
to cut again three men in that area got
to get it perfectly in the Gap to get a
boundary
[Applause]
nice line hard to freeze hands back of
the length
smartly played as well happy to take
your single good Baba
used his bowl as well used his Spinners
very well
still has one over of uh more than I was
when does he use it
and good delivery
it's a good comeback after that boundary
first ball
[Applause]
uh telling him no we already had one run
out
another one will be one too many
way on the onside just a single good
over Pakistan's point of view seven
conceded 90 for four
two is the call
and he'll get it easily
is really focused now he is in he has a
job on his hand
let's hear what he has to say did you
wake up excited for these kind of games
and you feel grateful that you're you're
part of this game in a way that you're
playing the game and you know not just
watching it as a spectator so you also
feel very grateful for the opportunity
[Applause]
whether he's out there in the Middle
with an opportunity
for sure
[Applause]
what that again if you're at
on like up Third Man Out
it's been a brilliant partnership and
giving themselves a chance India there's
no doubt about it
all week it's early and under the pump
play the conditions well Pakistan
deserves so much credit for the way
they're bowled and even to manage really
to get to that total one set a target of
160 after being under so much pressure
early
in the fielded world the ground Fielding
has been good
it's a good partnership though
their time and then it was hardik Pander
who cut loose there are probably
followed
using his feet a flurry of sixes that
set the tone
on the wrong side of the floor plenty
more needed of that because this
required rate
still a steep one
oh the shot
quick hands good risk
once again playing conditions
beautifully comes down the weekend
it's in a couple of slow balls and he's
over so if you're at Peaks this is not
going to be off base it's going to be
quick comes down the Wicket gets it
angled into the stamps and bang beats
that man at 45 he knows it's four
not the worst delivery
straight but geez it's a good shot
[Applause]
all these players know that in the final
overs they can really up the anti a
dangerous players uh
being in the in these situations quite
often
it's just securing that uh
they reach a stage where they know all
they have no choice but to go
even now RAV they got wickets in hand
only four down but you're about to hit
the 15th over Mark so they can afford
the last five to go as hard as they like
different when it was the 10th over
yes and with Dinesh Karthik still to
come
[Applause]
10 off the over
100 comes up for the loss of four
it's hot in the combox as well
I think the game
rests on the two hours that artistro has
to go
his partnership with 69.
[Applause]
harsrove is the death bowler for
Pakistan we haven't seen that slow one
yet which is
pretty brilliant but he's decided to
just smash the pitch
12 and over required and you feel
India need a big over something 15 16
even more
next couple need two there's one over
from Nawaz left
be interesting to see how Barber is
playing that one Nawaz over
[Applause]
and they get one for the throw they
can't just a single
they won't run on the overthrow
59 now 28.
a brilliant with the ball today are a
throw short of a land
and just kept banging it in
kept its simple as Pace was up and that
helped him
[Applause]
well go down as the defining moment he
was looking very good
now to Coley
football again
remember saying before this tournament
started
Pakistan's two key cricketers didn't
think what is one and barber I thought
it was Shaheen Afridi at the top and
alishra with the back end
[Music]
he's pumped his bowling quick that last
ball was 148.
[Music]
and both of those hard ovals as I'll
drove in the power play at that back end
closing in exhaust pre-delivery is just
a single
that's what happens with the extra Pace
the ball hurrying onto the bat and now
they'll be doing their calculations just
two runs from this over they know they
need at least 10 and then hope for a big
finish
[Applause]
the hardik has no option but to play the
boundary shot now middle overs
69 for one India and those nine
but the first six just 31 for three
after ten they were 45.
in both straight
through the offside maybe is the
opportunity for hardik
oh dear he did get a glove to it though
did rizwan
but that will be called wide there's
nothing that dampens the spirit of a
field inside
then a wide that goes for four it's five
runs and the ball is encountered
and this is brilliant from rizwan though
he's made sure that he saved the
boundary just a little bit of glove on
it
that would might well have been five
wise if it wasn't for flying rizwan
they have two there five of the over now
two balls to come still
[Applause]
it's a fine over so far
in every delivery that doesn't go to the
fence that required rate jumps up now
it's 13.2
remember Harris Road still has another
seven deliveries to go the powers are
not banking on him to close the Innings
out and apply as much pressure as
possible and make it easier for the rest
well he's done phenomenally this over
yeah
young man hasn't seen a lot of
a lot of cricket
he's both three overs for 17 so far
just five from this over
I think he's he's searching for the two
they won't get the two they won't get
the two
in retrospect it might have been on but
you can't look in retrospect 106 for
four
[Applause]
single
done he's done well there crammed the
batsman for room this is good bowling
yeah Baba holding that over of Nawaz
back he knows that
Pakistan could possibly close it out
in the next couple of hours now holy on
strike
boundary riders in front of the wicket
third and final leg in the circle
wants to go over the top the timing
isn't great but he does go over the top
should come back for two
[Applause]
it's just ticking away it's not it's not
quite speeding for for India this game
it's ticking but it's moving
yeah they need a couple of blows they
need boundaries now Pakistan will be
happy with every delivery that doesn't
go to the fence
for that boundary option goalie will
have to look behind the wicked
Point short third fine leg
[Applause]
swing enemies
I think he was looking to go over Third
Man you'd see the field was at shot
third both of them
standing outside just coming in as the
ball is about to be delivered so this is
what Virat is seeing deep mid Wicket
it's a long distance away somewhere far
away in the distance is deep midwicket
he'll have to stray in his eyes to see
long gone
a very good looking shot but it's only a
single ride we just heard Smithy that
there's 90
238 people down it's 239 now now that
you're gone is it cold can you feel the
heat in the stadium well actually it is
241 now because Ravi shastri's joined me
down here as well so it is cold it is
cold hash you stay up there don't worry
you stay nice and warm up there we'll
just get the tension the icy tension
down at ground level here you can feel
it though you can sense it it is just
brilliant the crowd are loving it
foreign
[Applause]
they need a boundary in all seriousness
India need a boundary these are two
terrific plays at the crease
but even the crowd the knowledgeable
ones and the crowd know that ones are
not gonna get it done
this has been a terrific over of bowling
and the and the previous one from
artistrove only four so far
hardik
but taking one for the throw Virat will
get there doesn't hurt Pakistan that
just two runs of it six game from it
it's one one two for four
[Music]
at the same point Pakistan 125-7 it
started to move ahead
India 112 for four
[Music]
it's really always wanted down there
have you seen real quality face how does
it look like from down there the face
that these three borders are generating
oh that's the quickest pitch I'm saying
in this competition so far without doubt
it's been carry throughout you only have
to look just how far back Muhammad
ruswan is
his confidence gonna get carried there
he's backed that far also because he's
trying to cut off the ramp shot that
goes fine does it but there is genuine
Pace in this pitch we'll see it now
puts it in the Gap gets it over
50 comes up
for Virat Kohli
he's a run machine when it comes to
playing against Pakistan let us land at
about 15 yards away to my right and I
believe it's landed inside the line
inside the barrier just
glad you're getting the replay right
this is uh this is Smith vision
Smith vision is spot on
that's four
cheese maybe your eyes are getting
sharper with Edge
oh one bit far away I said it'll be fear
but every one of those is crucial every
one of those is crucial we are going
close here
you were gonna call something very close
to a super over here hashaboglay no
Smithy no Smithy you and super always
50km of 43 balls but a boundary of the
first
wide down the lake side Shaheen Afridi
is the pressure telling just a little
bit they've got loads of runs in the
bank but just seems a precious telling a
little
[Applause]
India want this to be the over it's
about time you can't really afford
another one of those where they don't
get a big over
has to be
first delivery going for five
beautifully ball now Coley wants to is
very quick between the wickets
he just manufactures runs against
Pakistan his average is 67 the strike
rate is a little low but he just keeps
scoring runs and today's held this
Innings together question is can you now
give it the finishing kick
thank you
[Applause]
seven of the over so far from two
squeezes it all up it's in the Gap there
but does it have enough to go to the
boundary it's a bit of a race it goes
through Virat Kohli hits another
boundary it's 11 of the over from three
[Applause]
backing away turning on Virat Kohli now
Giants are pretty trying to follow him
but he's been able to just maneuver it
over extra Kaba
this is fabulous bearing
be able to place it and time it so well
that he gets another boundary
of India left it till too late or is
there still a huge twist in this story
now Shaheen Afridi is going back he's
going over the wicked
[Applause]
hurried up on him
he wants a second hard dick says no I'll
handle the strike for a while
how noisy is it Smithy down there well
you wouldn't heard the call you have to
use hand signals out there hasha it's
impossible to hear anything to be fair
that is just it as I said before in
commentary
hands down the most amazing atmosphere I
have ever heard of the game of cricket
ever
and stuff in rugby but it couldn't be as
noisy as this no it couldn't be it could
not be
seriously this is special
now what can hardik do here 37-32
well balled again the hitting that
banging into the middle of the wicket
yes work that length has worked
especially against hardik they've been
able to pull that short ball and the
slow bouncer
which has been difficult to get away
13 off the over but they still need more
he looks like we might be carrying a bit
of a nickel too
running might be a factor if they have
to
they're not going to win it by running
though Smithy
13 of this over
ly goes over the infield for four that's
the over they wanted Gerard Coley is
turning it on in style here and the
stadium is dancing to his Beats it's 129
before 31 needed of two
[Applause]
yeah beautiful place this time the short
one we are just getting inside it and
helping it over
yo that India needed they need more but
Murad has turned it on
[Music]
the same point Pakistan was six ahead
coming down to that dreaded 19 dollar
but it's dreaded 19 to an India bowling
and as you'd imagine it's already Shroff
this is the old for the match for
Pakistan
[Music]
14 15 at least of this one
right bazid what's he going to do you've
seen so much of various going to pull
the slow ones into the deck the quick
Hawkers
[Applause]
I think it's going to be into the deck
even if it's slow it's still going to be
into the deck
find leg is up but third man is out on
the boundary for the uppercut
let's put that in the Gap no he hasn't
just the single but it's viratus turning
it on who's now back in strike
but I said I've got a question with you
who both the last over who has the
bowler last over
I think
oh no he's finished oh he's got one from
Nawaz left yes exactly
so
[Applause]
our stroke doesn't want to go for 14-15
that's what Barbara is thinking Irish
roof can just go for maybe 10 12 and
that leads enough for Nawaz
on test
single
two in the Asia cup and artist Ralph
both the 19th and I think pandeya got 14
of that leaving just six for Nawaz to
bowl the last over
[Music]
foreign
[Applause]
Partnership of 75 they have come back
into the game but there's still a lot to
do
what Mrs Mrs hardik's been be calmed a
little bit I didn't think you'd say that
with him and Virat bedding
this is brilliant from Harris
one banged into the pitch he's gone for
that delivery more often than not
because of the surface because of the
way hardik plays he's attacked him that
way
how many from the last over does he
leave uh he's got to leave he's got to
leave if he can
if he can he's got to leave 18 I believe
18. there you go we've seen a 20 over a
couple of times
[Applause]
29 still
hurries up on him no timing at all is
Virat gonna go for two no viratel take
the strike this is outstanding from
Irish Rove so far 28 of eight
second
is trying to hit that short link too far
in front of the ground I would be
surprised that ferrat Kohli uses that
pace in a different fashion pretty hard
to combat that flat batting down the
ground
[Applause]
there's a third man down there who's so
fine for the uppercut but fine leg is
inside the circle
they're looking for power
goes down the ground goalie goes out of
the ground
wow this is a sensational hit from Virat
Kohli
68-49 is turning it on is this the Virat
Kohli you could score a run some time
back he's come back in some Style
what a shot this is
a slow one into the pitch and he's just
stood tall on top of the bounce and he's
hit it big
with almost a straight back
India needed this they need another one
but this is quality
what a big delivery in the context of
the game you talk about 240 balls
this is so big now third man is coming
up fine leg is dropped back
come on
they want to keep Pena on strike
Pakistan whatever happens here
[Applause]
he has what a way to end it on his
revolver that was looking so good two
sixes India now needs 16 Hope Springs
are new what a game we've got 144 for 4
16 to get
yeah this is the man strong Virat Kohli
last couple of deliveries this time just
a flick let the ball come on
glass off the man deposits that into the
stands he knows those two deliveries
have brought India back they needed it
it's still not done but India are back
13 the partnership now from 79. Smithy
who said 18 at 16 Smithy of the last
over that was the second ass delivery
will look long in my mind that shot is
not an impossible for a Norman human
being to hit that link back down over
the bowler's head on a very long
boundary for six was quite astonishing
that forced the error hopefully in the
last delivery and I always knew that
he'd use the pace to his Advantage down
the ground down past fine League this
guy is a genius he might not win it but
he's a genius
you just love the pressure there are
some people who get buoyed by pressure
there's some people look at burdened by
it I think Goldie gets buoyed under
pressure
[Applause]
blasted water I mean I know somebody
talked about the one down the ground you
don't always see Virat played this one
over fine leg
yeah 16 to get left arm spin
hardik will fancy himself really
with spin on
there's so much discussion so much
pressure riding on these first couple of
deliveries and look where Muhammad
rizwan is standing to spin
the keepers four to five meters back
how would that be still Smitty they do
not want
to steal one they do not want him to
work it fine they want to keep hardik
paneer on strike that is what they've
been talking about
Isaac is a fabulous player of spin but
he's struggling a bit to their 40 of 36.
right here we go 16 to get from six
balls 90 000 people at MCG got us how
many millions around the world and what
a spectacle you've had so far
cover is long and deep long gone and
long off right behind the bowler so is a
very straight midwicket here's the first
ball it's a Miss hit it's a mishead
the catch is taken it means the new
batsman is in strike Virat Kohli thinks
he's crossed over it doesn't matter this
is a huge ball Muhammad Nawaz has
delivered
yeah I wanted to go Lakeside swung
through
maybe trying to hit it too hard but
doesn't matter nobody cares really
because it's just gone in the air
not trying to spit it is no us
yeah it's Barber keeps calm takes the
catch it's a DOT ball you Bassman all
strike Pakistan now
with the ascendancy
are they for 48 144 for five
[Music]
37 years old in his Karthik is that a
wonderful day as a wicket keeper but
these are the situations that you dream
of
sometimes people think you're 37 years
old you should be watching other people
play but his perseverance his
determination he's worked hard and now
he's coming to a situation it's very
cold out in the middle but we've got to
turn the heat on and get 16 or five well
does he does he hasha what have they
talked about what have they talked about
what has Coley said to him give it to me
just get one give it to me I can win
this the way I'm hitting it or does he
say be bold be brave you go
is in the side to do that he takes a
single then it's only
15 or four then you need four boundaries
it's a fabulous result for Pakistan this
first ball and remember you cannot cross
over anymore the new batsman is in what
does Karthik do he plays The Sweep shot
very well
[Music]
not much power he had made up his mind
early on it's a wonderful start for
Pakistan
Coley wants to know who is scoring for
height
is having nothing over
yeah he just signal that
DK was halfway down the track so
no no ball four deliveries 15 to get now
we're out on strike Virat has been the
one who's been hitting the boundaries
not been heartache it's been veeran
for the right man in terms
especially for India on strike right now
it needs two sixes
the boundary the fours won't do now he
needs two sixes what's the field now run
longoff straight long gone straight
shadab is in the middle of it all at
Deep mid we get very straight cover very
straight the bigots down the ground are
all covered 15 or four
goalie goes down the ground he'll only
get a single he's Karthik gonna come
running back they need Virat Kohli and
strike
Dives is he 37 foot reel completes the
second but now it's 13 of threes
yeah just getting to that moment now
they need sixes this ball has to go to
the fence
Pakistan
and almost see that line the end is near
don't Bola Noble they're telling Nawaz
don't go the wide look where the Wicket
keeper is stride back
they don't want any buys
[Applause]
number six
now it's he's asking for the height how
high was that ball they've got the six
of the over
now it's down to seven from two Gerard
Kohli wanted the strike he got the
strike unprecedented scenes here at the
Melbourne cricket ground it's been
called a no ball
it's a no ball in the six
we've seen everything
tonight
[Applause]
tell there's a huge discussion going
long
yeah
to give him some help here
right the Square Lake umpire has to make
the call
again
these are very very
emotional scenes here Baba is not happy
at all
Mario erasma says his great ability to
calm things down
they need six of three now is there
another twist in this game it's India's
at the moment
was that about waste high was it the
umpires rule so it's six of three now
six or three and how the pendulum swings
towards India again
[Applause]
demanded the no ball straight away
he wanted to do it of the earlier ball
too Dinesh Karthik at the non-strike his
end is waiting now we're at the game is
in your grasp Nawaz has three balls to
go
six to get what we're not going to do
here that's wide five to get now the
pressure is on the bowler who would have
believed that this game would have that
Sensational twist as this one this match
was gone it was in Pakistan's pocket and
Virat Kohli
is pulling it out at the moment but
there's still five to get and it's still
a three hit
rally holds all the aces right now he's
been brilliant five of three now
as he believed do Pakistan believe
he's knocked him over but then take the
run it's running away down but surely if
it hit the ball with his the stumps
they're coming back for three
they get three of it
was a free hit remember it was a free
hit
yeah inquiry now rizwan doesn't like it
it is
let's hit the stumps on the ball should
be dead
it was a free hitter
so they've run three
[Applause]
what's it like down there that's crazy
it's grown man damn it crying summer
puzzled summer jubilant Ravi shastri is
standing right next to me I don't think
he's seen anything like this ninety
thousand ninety thousand you think it's
fairly for money three buys
suddenly Pakistan are staying down
defeated cleaning up the ball ricocheted
and Murat kept running saw the DK
and he came back for the Third
calm down where are the same calm down
he said it's not always that he says
calm down but there's two of two
what does Dinesh Karthik do here Virat
kohli's off strike for Pakistan but he's
off strike with just two to get off two
it was that no ball for height
eventually
Ryan how are they going to play does he
tell Dinesh Karthik go for it what if he
misses does he say take a single let's
level the scores and give it back to me
what's happened here is rizwan has now
come up for the stunts because they need
to get kartik out they need to get him
out and that brings a new player out if
Coley can't get back on strike so that's
why he's come up to the stunts for a
genuine dismissal the medium pace it's
not work it hasn't been accurate enough
trust the keeper to spot what the keeper
is doing here where does Karthik get the
single would that be his first goal
because Smithy is absolutely spot on
a wicket here and the new batsman comes
in with Pakistan still having a run in
the bank
okay what have you got The Big Field the
big
field is spread out
three on the onside there's still only
four inside the circle
this game is still alive but only just
all eyes on Dinesh Karthik all eyes on
Muhammad Nawaz
no is there a stumping is there a
stumping what a Twist are we seeing a
cricket match or what Dinesh karthik's
got a walk backs with the Euro spot on
the new version of big strike copy
umpire review for stumping TV on party
director we have an Umpire review for
stumping from foot checks it's a fair
delivery you can move on to front on
spin Vision please
that that was the moment for Dinesh
Karthik but it wasn't to be respond has
been fantastic behind the scenes for
spin vision
now
keep that rolling through please
foreign
now where did he take the ball here keep
that rolling through please keep it
rolling through please keep it rolling
through I'm ready with my decision for
the big screen
[Music]
[Applause]
comes in
singers
he's going to say it are we
what does Ashwin do though
try and hit it as you just try and take
the one
or does he that's what happened try and
get a boundary that's what happens if
you put Smithy down then we mentioned
the super order a little while back
Pakistan can hit field is on the
boundary I've got to hit the man off the
boundary they can't let them run too
because they'll try they will try if
they get the chance they've got to be
hunting in closer over the top Soviet
he's pulled it back he has pulled it
back nowaz it's a wide
[Applause]
[Music]
nakistan now it's got to be a super over
if they have to win it and that was very
very clever from ravichandran Ashwin he
quickly realized the ball was outside
the Lake's dumb they didn't back away
stayed where he was there was thought
that he'd back away and he tried to
follow him
now India just need one
game just keeps giving and giving his
spin stupendous this last over
right everybody's inside everybody's
inside to cut the single now what
they've got to ensure is look for the
run out opportunity at the non-strikers
end with Ashwin running there Kohli will
run
Nawaz are you watching by Virat is
inside the crease as you run into ball
the scores are level one run to get
there's still a couple of people out in
the Deep
infield
[Applause]
[Music]
India have been a famous win you look at
all the great wins over the years and I
think you'll find very very few to
compare with this one this game was gone
Virat Kohli pulled it back what a
champion what an absolute Champion
without goalie is and now ravichander
naswin keeps its cool produces the wide
then goes over this must be
heartbreaking for Pakistan but Smithy
down there there must be absolute
pandemonium
[Music]
did you see Coley's reaction he bit down
and he punched the first under the under
the pitch he has played so many special
winnings but what does this mean harsher
how high does this rate I think I'm
spotting a deer in Virat kohli's eyes
I've seen Virat Kohli play for so many
years I've seen some of his best Innings
but I have not seen a tear in his eyes
and I think I spotted a tear
Paul wicket
s
pulled it out of the bay India were
almost dead and buried with what an
Innings he's playing even in the last
over it's all been where I'd call the
Pakistan well they all think they've
been
taken away the victory from the hand
this is what you play for
when you've retired when everything is
done these are the moments you remember
and Ashwin how clever was Ashwin after
India lost Dinesh Karthik
and now Virat the king
we'll just look around this packed
Melbourne cricket ground Rohit Sharma
watch your back but
it matter today
isn't it 90
000 people are singing and cheering and
dancing here
this was Pakistan's game
goes back to the hussy moments it goes
back to the Wade moments and now it
comes to the Kohli moments they've got
to come fighting back this is difficult
to digest now 48 in the last three
Pakistan were way in front and this man
just kept coming and coming and kept
them in the hunt and in the end it was
because of him that India now celebrates
most of this 90
000 attendants in the crowd celebrate
water
game we've just witnessed Pakistan well
they made a few comebacks in the game it
just went one way and the other and in
the end the class of the man prevailed
I remember saying when Robert is out of
bomb it's always England
to the rescue for Virat Kohli it's
always Australia he loves playing in
these conditions but his record against
Pakistan is astonishing
whose record against Pakistan and he has
pulled this match out of absolutely
nowhere you look down their total 160
for six Virat kohli's played 53 walls
for 82.
these Virat it is Innings like these
that take you beyond the present and
into Legend
This Is The Stuff Legend is made up
forget it was Ashwin with the winning
hit the field was in he kept to school
just time the shot didn't try to hit it
too hard
and he knew straight away he had done
enough
240 balls basically they came down to
one no ball an inch over maybe that's
all it came down to
in the Roar from Virat Kohli
punching the ground
there's so much bottled up inside Virat
Kohli that is where the tear would came
out
hardik knew he was struggling and hardik
was struggling viraj was the one who
picked up the Baton
welcome at the Earth come at the stage
cometh the man
four of us to go what did you punch into
the computer garage
well um
if this stop talking I I can't hear
well um we're not before you start
you have to collect the award from Mr
Bean thank you sir thank you very much
player of the match tell us well um
it's a
it's a surreal atmosphere
um I honestly have no words I have no
idea how that happened
um I heard they kept telling me you know
just believe in believe we can do it
stay till the end
um I honestly I'm lost for words no you
had a good partnership going which was
much needed when did you decide you both
had to go oh one had to go well uh I
think when Shaheen bowled from this end
the Pavilion end that's when I kind of
spoke to hardik that we need to take him
down and then the conversation was
simple he said Nawaz has to bowl one
over so I told him if I can take Harris
down
then they will kind of you know panic
because he's their Prime bowler so I was
kind of pumping myself up to hit two
sixes when we needed 28 of it and that
became 16 of six so I mean
I I'm kind of lost for words I have no
idea two special shots of Harris Road
you know what's that anticipation or
prevented it had to be premeditated yeah
um it's just instinctively I I saw the
and I told myself just stay still the
one I had long on was unexpected it was
back Overland slower ball and then the
next one I
I just you know uh just swung my bat
through the line of the ball and it just
flew over fine leg
and now standing here I just feel like
this was meant to be I mean it's it's a
very very special moment where does the
settings rank in your T20 career
well um
I've till today I've always said Mohali
was my best Innings against Australia I
got 82 or 52 today I got 82 or 53. so
they're absolute
they
exactly the same innings
but I think today I will count this one
Higher because of the magnitude of the
game and what the situation was it
seemed impossible but then hard they
kept pushing me in that partnership and
we just went deep
and it just happened an award for this
crowd
oh it's phenomenal thank you so much
you guys
you guys have um
supported me shown me so much love and
support for all these months that I was
kind of struggling you guys kept backing
me and um
I'm very grateful for your support thank
you
[Applause]
congratulations you've lit up this world
cup thank you so much